<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>psychosomatic.co.za</title>
    <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za" />
    <updated>2025-03-18T13:41:14+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za</id>

    <entry>
        <title>WHAT HAPPENED?!</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/what-happened/"/>
        <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/what-happened/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-18T13:41:01+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There is a distinct difference between incident occurence in our lives and how we recall those incidents occuring. Our emotional&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>There is a distinct difference between incident occurence in our lives and how we recall those incidents occuring. Our emotional state at the time of incident plays a large part in our choice, albeit subconscious, of how we remember incidents and occurences. Emotions can change towards " what happened" for a number of reasons.</p>
<p>Our conscious recollective memoric area of brain can only recall events with lucid clarity for a relatively compromised period of time. The selected emotion affiliated with an incident, perceived as either positive or negative, can also influence our "elected" recollection. Personality types too play a role specifically relative to incidents precipitating fight, flight or freeze responses.</p>
<p>Bottom line; The event which actually occured is vastly different in reality to our experiential response thereunto.</p>
<p>This is what makes my practice, Psycho-Somatic so profound. Using a unique method of separating event from experience of event allows you to recognize events, specifically those that have bothered you, and replace your historic perception of the past with a new, healthy productive memory.</p>
<p>This by no means implies that we remove or alter the past, we simply re-create the way YOU CHOOSE to revisit the past.</p>
<p>BINGO! New perspective on the past, new lease on the future. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>IT&#x27;S EASY TO BE UGLY</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/its-easy-to-be-ugly/"/>
        <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/its-easy-to-be-ugly/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-17T13:54:18+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It's easy to be ugly when you're insecure, feel threatened and lack confidence. I'ts easy to be ugly when others&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It's easy to be ugly when you're insecure, feel threatened and lack confidence. I'ts easy to be ugly when others are succeeding and you're not. It's easy to be ugly when others are living their truth and you're not. It's easy to be ugly when even a poor person seems happy enough. It's easy to be ugly when you feel victimised by life. It's easy to be ugly when the world, in its chaotic state, rips other people to spiritual pieces. It's easu to be ugly when people who are different from the "norm" in terms of colour, creet and gender identification. It's easy to climb on the ugly band wagon and join in the humuliation of innocent people who mean no harm and whose only "sin" is just trying to live in peace albeit with a skew face, a damaged physique, a toothless mouth and an old car.</p>
<p>Live YOUR truth. Rock YOUR truth. Let all others who do no harm live theirs.</p>
<p>www.psychosomatic.co.za </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>RELATIONSHIP CHECK</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/relationship-check/"/>
        <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/relationship-check/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-10T11:39:19+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    According to Psychology Stats, Approximately 85% of casual relationships, 70% of early relationships and 50% of long - term relationships&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>According to Psychology Stats, Approximately 85% of casual relationships, 70% of early relationships and 50% of long - term relationships FAIL!</p>
<p>The problem?!..lack of commitment, unmet expectations and compatability issues.</p>
<p>It is thus difficult and stressful to feel comfortable being open, honest and authentic about our deeper feelings. Lies often become the norm as fear of rejection reigns forth and wreaks havoc.</p>
<p>www.psychosomatic.co.za</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>THE VOICE OF THE CONSCIENCE</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/the-voice-of-the-conscience/"/>
        <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/the-voice-of-the-conscience/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-06T12:18:09+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The voice of your conscience is what your inner truth sounds like. it tells you who you are, what you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The voice of your conscience is what your inner truth sounds like. it tells you who you are, what you should do, how you should live, how you should love. It is the voice that raises red flags, the voice that notifies you of stop streets. This voice is called intuition. It sets the parameter between feeling and thinking. It is your sensible instinct.</p>
<p>The more you listen to this vital voice, the less it speaks. </p>
<p>Minimize your ego and maximize your sense.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>DreamScape</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/dreamscape/"/>
        <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/dreamscape/</id>

        <updated>2025-03-05T12:31:01+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've had a vision for some time now. Can you imagine a customised non-contact device that tracks your dream activity&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've had a vision for some time now. Can you imagine a customised non-contact device that tracks your dream activity construct across the four areas of your brain associated thereunto, irrespective of the numerous positions that your head and body assumes during sleep?! </p>
<p>You'de be able to wake up in the morning, press a button on your cranial tracker and download your dreams to a pod which connects to your computer or TV seemlessly, allowing you to replay your dreams with the exactness in every detail as to how they occured in your sleep prior.</p>
<p>Ahead of its time?!..Perhaps, but one thing's for certain..Our dream material is useful in determining our underlying emotions and states of mind.</p>
<p>In the meantime, my practice has some amazing solutions to a host of diverse challenges which you may be experiencing.</p>
<p>Visit www.psychosomatic.co.za</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>See the light</title>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Jules S Greenstein</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/see-the-light/"/>
        <id>https://www.psychosomatic.co.za/posts/see-the-light/</id>

        <updated>2025-02-22T13:11:33+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Pearls of wisdom that I discovered in the oyster shells collected by wise people and given to me. I shall&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Pearls of wisdom that I discovered in the oyster shells collected by wise people and given to me.</p>
<p>I shall be posting these gathered pearls of wisdom on my blog on my website so as to share with you and thus inspire you.</p>
<p>Please take time to peruse my website and should you require any further assistance, please consult the options on the menu. Albeit PTSD, relationship and Intimacy issues, academic improvement or Sports performance management, we've got this. See the light.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
